#### Contact

temidayo322@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/temidayo-fagbuaro-acicrm-ccsp-b1bb42107 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Lead Generation Chatbot Responses Messaging

## Languages

Yoruba (Native or Bilingual) English (Native or Bilingual) French (Elementary)

### Certifications

Customer Service Certificate
Youth Entrepreneurship Program
Customer Service and Relationship
Management (CSRM)
Associate Member

EFSET English Certificate 71/100 (C2 Proficient )

#### Honors-Awards

Award of Recognition

# Temidayo Fagbuaro ACICRM, CCSP

CX professional | Humanitarian | Creative Writer Nigeria

# Summary

I am a freelance professional Customer Service Representative specializing in remote call center services, Virtual Assistant, telemarketing, appointment scheduling, cold calling, Data Entry, and other back-end office projects.

I am a dedicated and very proactive person willing to meet and exceed any given target.

If you need a Virtual Assistant, Call Center Agent or someone to handle your contact center, manage your customers, answer questions and inquiries, handle incoming and outgoing calls, or administrative work like email, chat, and data entry then look no further. I work with any time zone and location is not an issue.

Also, I am a seasoned creative writer born out of love and passion for writing.

## Experience

RWS Group Al Trainer April 2024 - Present (3 months)

TELUS International AI Data Solutions AI community Member May 2022 - Present (2 years 2 months)

TYD Outsourcing Solutions
Supervisor
June 2020 - Present (4 years 1 month)

https://temiloveblog.wordpress.com Creative Writer March 2017 - Present (7 years 4 months)

amfa FOUNDATION Field Operations Volunteer June 2019 - May 2024 (5 years) Nigeria

Grupo Noa International
Customer Service Representative (Remote)
November 2022 - April 2024 (1 year 6 months)

Grupo Noa International
Customer Service/Data Entry Agent (Remote)
May 2021 - January 2022 (9 months)
United States

Unateus
Call Center Operator/Telemarketer (Remote)
June 2020 - April 2021 (11 months)
Moscow City, Russia

Directorate of Field Operations (APC)
Call Centre Agent
January 2019 - February 2019 (2 months)
Abuja FCT

Creative Imagination Press Limited
Administrative Secretary
November 2015 - April 2018 (2 years 6 months)
Abuja-Nigeria

Nigerian Export Promotion Council (NEPC)
Graduate Intern
October 2015 - October 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Nigerian Export Promotion Council (NEPC)
P. A to the Admin and HR Deputy Director (National Youth Service)
June 2014 - February 2015 (9 months)

Abuja- Nigeria

# Education

University of California, Berkeley Edxonline, Academic and Business Writing (2019)

Adekunle Ajasin University
Bachelor of Arts - BA(Hons), English and Literary Studies · (2012)

Chartered Institute of Customer Relationship Management Associate

Peace Operations Training Institute

Principles and Guidelines for UN Peacekeeping Operations · (2019 - 2020)

Alao French Centre Diploma, French · (2012 - 2013)